MAHSHA DESSIAM ADNI

Semarang, Indonesia | Whatsapp: 0895325233938 | Email: mahshadessiamadni@gmail.com | https://www.linkedin.com/in/mahsha-dessiam-adni-415b30216

SUMMARY

Mahsha is an undergraduate student at Universitas Dian Nuswantoro. She is a person who is very passionate, responsible, and disciplined towards something that has been made a commitment. She is able to work under pressure independently or with a team, it could be said she can adapt to all conditions and situations. She can easily adapt in various work environments and various kinds of work. She has tried various positions in several team divisions, such as staff, secretary, and also moderator.

EXPERIENCE

BEM-KM (Badan Eksekutif Mahasiswa Keluarga Mahasiswa) (October 2022 - Present)Secretary of Ministry of Foreign Affairs

- Take a note of annual meeting
- Coordinating relations with external of BEM-KM
- Cooperate with outside parties of BEM-KM

Startup Campus (August - December 2022)

Students of UI/UX Designer track

- Use Figma design, toolbar, prototype present, plugin, figma community, and figma jamm
- Make design illustrations using information architecture, crazy 8's, and wireframes.
- Make design prototypes using prototyping tools
- Create product design and designs mockup UI design

EnglishLearner.id (September - December 2021)

Secretary of Event Organizer division

- Make and plan various kinds of events that are interesting for social media users.
- Coordinating and managing an annual meeting and events.

HMTI (Himpunan Mahasiswa Teknik Informatika) (December 2020 - March 2021)

Staff of the Information and Communication division.

- Communicate and work together as a team or with other divisions to make a project or event.
- Forward various information regarding HMTI and those related to the course of study to students in a timely and clear manner.
- Communicating with other divisions regarding participant-related matters, invitation letters, and technical issues for the smooth running of the event.

Gathering HMTI (Himpunan Mahasiswa Teknik Informatika)

Game Staff

- Create and develop games that can create bonding between participants in their respective groups.
- Communicating and collaborating with other divisions for the continuity of the event.
- Think creatively and find ideas for games that are fun and not boring in groups.
- Guide the game by group and ensure that the game runs well, and build an exciting atmosphere.

EDUCATION

SMA Negeri 1 Rembang (2017 - 2020)

Natural Science - 88

Universitas Dian Nuswantoro (2020 - Present)

Computer science

SKILLS

- UI/UX Design
- Creativity
- Problem Solving

- Creative thinking
- Team Work
- Communication
- Flexibility
- EmphatyHTML, JS, CSS, PHP, Java